("Dark Horse" by Katy Perry)
♪ Yeah y'all know what it is ♪
♪ Katy Perry ♪
♪ Juicy J ♪
♪ Uh huh let's rage ♪
♪ I knew you were ♪
♪ You were gonna come to me ♪
♪ And here you are ♪
♪ But you better choose carefully ♪
♪ 'Cause I I'm capable of anything ♪
♪ Of anything and everything ♪
♪ Make me your Aphrodite ♪
♪ Make me your one and only ♪
♪ But don't make me your enemy ♪
♪ Your enemy your enemy ♪
♪ So you wanna play with magic ♪
♪ Boy you should know
what you're fallin' for ♪
♪ Baby do you dare to do this ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm coming at
you like a dark horse ♪
♪ Are you ready for ready for ♪
♪ A perfect storm perfect storm ♪
♪ 'Cause once you're
mine once you're mine ♪
♪ There's no going back ♪
♪ Mark my words ♪
♪ This love will make you levitate ♪
♪ Like a bird like a bird without a cage ♪
♪ But down to earth ♪
♪ If you choose to walk
away don't walk away ♪
♪ It's in the palm of your hand now baby ♪
♪ It's a yes or a no no maybe ♪
♪ So just be sure before
you give it all to me ♪
♪ All to me give it all to me ♪
♪ So you wanna play with magic ♪
♪ Boy you should know
what you're fallin' for ♪
♪ Baby do you dare to do this ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm coming at
you like a dark horse ♪
♪ Are you ready for ready for ♪
♪ A perfect storm perfect storm ♪
♪ 'Cause once you're
mine once you're mine ♪
♪ There's no going back ♪
♪ Uh she's a beast ♪
♪ I call her Karma ♪
♪ She eat your heart out
like Jeffrey Dahmer ♪
♪ Be careful try not to lead her on ♪
♪ Shawty heart is on steroids ♪
♪ 'Cause her love is so strong ♪
♪ You might fall in
love when you meet her ♪
♪ If you get the chance
you better keep her ♪
♪ She's sweet as pie but
if you break her heart ♪
♪ She turn cold as a freezer ♪
♪ That fairy tale ending with
a knight in shining armor ♪
♪ She can be my Sleeping Beauty ♪
♪ I'm gon' put her in a coma ♪
♪ Damn I think I love her ♪
♪ Shawty so bad I'm
sprung and I don't care ♪
♪ She ride me like a roller coaster ♪
♪ Turn the bedroom into a fair ♪
♪ Her love is like a drug ♪
♪ I was tryna hit it and quit it ♪
♪ But lil' mama so dope ♪
♪ I messed around and got addicted ♪
♪ So you wanna play with magic ♪
♪ Boy you should know
what you're fallin' for ♪
♪ Baby do you dare to do this ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm coming at
you like a dark horse ♪
♪ Are you ready for ready for ♪
♪ A perfect storm perfect storm ♪
♪ 'Cause once you're
mine once you're mine ♪
♪ There's no going back ♪
(panting)